<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo &amp; Sheri's Homes and Lifestyle Real Estate Video Blog</title>
    <description>Our mission at Hugo &amp; Sheri's Homes and Lifestyle is to be your best resource for Southern California real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Hugo &amp; Sheri's Homes and Lifestyle, your professional Southern California Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 12:04:56 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 12:04:56 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Today's Shifting Market Similar To Our Last Peak? What We Learned From The Past</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rkRKgSVnJpM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s message, I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk about how changing markets can have varying effects on both buyers and sellers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last time the market peaked in 2005 and 2006, we started to notice an influx of headlines that talked about the market potentially collapsing. In the beginning, we brushed them off, but then the articles kept coming. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we started noticing a slowdown:  Homes were taking longer to sell, and sellers just looked the other way and kept doing things as if nothing had changed. &lt;strong&gt;It was very clear that something was changing&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the reason that prices started dropping slowly is that buyers who are searching at the top of the market will pause when things start to take a dip, and more sellers start putting their homes on the market because they also realize that we’ve reached the peak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Be preemptive and do something sooner rather than later.%20http://localhost:4000/is-todays-shifting-market-similar-to-our-last-peak-what-we-learned-from-the-past.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Be preemptive and do something sooner rather than later.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same thing is happening in today’s market. Prices are starting to shift because there is much more urgency for sellers to get their homes sold. When prices fall, the people who are really affected are 1. The move-up buyers who need a bigger home, and  2. Those who are getting ready to retire within the next few years. &lt;strong&gt;If your home value drops significantly, you will likely be stuck for 10-12 years—the typical market cycle from top to top&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My advice, if you want the most for your home, is to be preemptive and do something sooner rather than later&lt;/strong&gt;. If you are not in a hurry and don’t have to sell, time will work against you as the prices start accelerating down. I’m sure you are wondering how to attack this market and how to plan ahead and make sure that you come out on top. Don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/is-todays-shifting-market-similar-to-our-last-peak-what-we-learned-from-the-past.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/is-todays-shifting-market-similar-to-our-last-peak-what-we-learned-from-the-past.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To Our Blog!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our market remains busy, and it’s still an opportune time to command a high price selling your home.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know what’s happening in The Inland Empire, specifically pertaining to home values, that will directly affect you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we’ll be posting two monthly video messages on this blog to keep you updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will be valuable and useful in helping you stay on top of what’s happening in the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check back because content will be coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to keep you updated on what’s happening in The Inland Empire!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
